GORAN RADMANOVIC

Address:

1. Artiljerijskog Puka 17, 78400 Gradiska, Bosnia and Herzegovina

Email:

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

Summary

I'm a full stack web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience. I'm a quick learner and I work as a freelancer. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you. Hope to hear from you soon.

Experience

Frontend developer - 12/2020 to Present

Examiz, Remote

• I'm working remotely as a freelance frontend developer for Examiz company. As a frontend developer I'm working on the enterprise app soluition for HR managers inside big companies. Technology that I'm using are VueJS, JavaScript, HTML & SCSS, GIT, JIRA ect.

Web developer - 06/2020 to 05/2021

Webimpacto, Remote

• I was working remotely as web developer on eCommerce solutions build in PrestaShop platform. Installing and configuring modules, fixing bugs and other things. Technology that I'm using are PHP, Symfony framework, HTML & CSS, JS, GIT ect.

Web developer (freelance) - 07/2019 to 04/2021

OOMovers, Remote

• I was working remotely as a full stack web developer for company specialize in moving. My responsibility is to develop, maintain and upgrade company's website. Technology that I'm using are PHP & Silex framework, JS, HTML & CSS, SCSS, GIT ect.

Frontend Web developer - 03/2019 to 07/2019

Kompitenz, Banja Luka

• I worked as frontend web developer on frontend part of B2B web platform for one of the biggest Germany dairy industry. The web platform was connecting dairy manufacturer and the dairy industry as a buyer. Tech stack that I was using on that project was PHP (Laravel) and the VueJS as a frontend, and also SASS as CSS preprocessor.

Freelance Web developer - 11/2018 to 03/2019

Freelance (remote), Gradiska

• I worked on various web development project as full stack developer with technology stack mostly of PHP and JavaScript, project are different from classic web apps to moder PWA apps.

Web developer - 04/2016 to 11/2018

AleaControl, Banja Luka

• I worked on the frontend part of the betting and gambling apps for casinos and bookmaker. Also I was in contact with programmers from partner's company and with our clients from casinos and betting house. And one of my responsibility was to develop and maintain company's website. Main technology which I used was JS and AngularJS, HTML & CSS, GIT.

Web developer - 04/2016 to 11/2018

AleaControl, Banja Luka

• I worked on the frontend part of the betting and gambling apps for casinos and bookmaker. Also I was in contact with programmers from partner's company and with our clients from casinos and betting house. And one of my responsibility was to develop and maintain company's website. Main technology which I used was JS and AngularJS, HTML & CSS, GIT.

Lecture at the Course web development - 09/2017 to 11/2017 and 07/2018 to 09/2018

Business Garden, Banja Luka

• I worked as a lecturer at the initial course of web development where I taught students to the basics of HTML and CSS technology.

PHP Web developer - 10/2015 to 03/2016

BitLab, Banja Luka

I worked on the web pages and web apps for clients. I also maintained legacy code. In addition, I worked in a team of developers and the main technologies that I used were PHP & Laravel framework, HTML & CSS, and also JavaScript.

Intern - 11/2014 to 12/2014

OgoSense, Banja Luka

• I have successfully completed the program OGO Sense practices in the field of IT support and maintenance with focus on Client training and communication, Joomla CMS website management and CentOS administration.

Intern - 09/2014 to 11/2014

E-Info, Banja Luka

• In this practice, I worked with MSSQL databases, I was introduced to the basics of Delphi programming language and creating a form for entering and collecting data from the database via the Delphi. Also, I was introduced to the design of the database via MSSQL, installing Windows and Linux OS systems and MSSQL Server installation. I also worked in Embarcadero Framework.

Census Instructor - 10/2013 to 11/2013 Census BIH/RS

- Managing and leading census team.
- Educating census taker.
- Census field work.

Commercial Manager - 04/2007 to 09/2013

Plastik d.o.o, Gradiska

- Selling a variety of plastic goods and items.
- Conducted client assessments.
- Supply and delivery of plastic goods.

Education

JavaScript Course - 10/2016 to 12/2016

ICBL, Banja Luka

Basic of JavaScript programming language.

PHP & MySQL Course - 12/2015 to 05/2015

ICBL, Banja Luka

PHP and web development.

WordPress Course - 07/2015 to 08/2015

ICBL, Banja Luka

Installing WordPress and creating WP websites.

Beginner JAVA Course – 01/2015 to 05/2015

ICBL, Banja Luka

Basic of JAVA programming language.

Team Work Course - 09/2014 to 11/2014

ICBL, Banja Luka

Course about working in the teams and large groups.

Beginner, Advanced and OOP PHP and MySQL Course – 05/2014 to 11/2015 **InfoARS**, Banja Luka

Learning about PHP and web development.

Graduated demographer – 10/2003 to 07/2008

Faculty of Science, Banja Luka

• Demography and Population studies.

Skill Highlights

- PHP & MySQL, Laravel, Twig, Slim
- REST API, Google Map API
- HTML & CSS, PUG, SASS
- JavaScript, ES6, AJAX, VueJS, Gulp, Webpack, Parcel, PWA, JSON,
- MySQL, Firebase, MongoDB
- GIT, GitHub, JIRA, Trello
- Windows, Linux

Languages

English – C1

Portfolio

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#projects

Hobbies

- Running
- Basketball
- Bicycling

- Blood donor
- Technology
- Video Games